Jhaal is
scared of the fluctuations in the stock market.
You are not alone, I am also scared.
Due to these fluctuations, many
investors will use it. Subscribers
and my friends have asked me
what is that technique by which we can do the stock front
part. In this,
Reddy stock market bank, no stock is
hundred percent clear. The ups and downs are
part of the blood relative market,
so definitely keep this in mind and
before investing in the stock market,
in the fluctuations, we can definitely identify such stocks in
which there is
more safety and less risk. To
know which one is that, definitely watch this video.
Friends, I would
like to share with you those five points in life which
you have to keep in mind initially. A.
before investing in stocks or before placing a stop
and before placing a stop, A.
share this friends that if you do
not want any loss of capital in any stop or you want to
limit the loss to a very low level, then share this
that you should invest in that stock for long-term
practice and
not only long-term, friends, do it only
in the form of reverse trading as well.  By this I mean
if you have to invest ₹100 in the whole year
then you divide that ₹100 in 12 months
so that your wrist gets spread. The
second thing that you have to keep in mind is that
she should stay away from all that has some
negative zone news or some fraud
news or impact of some regulations.
She should stay away from the talk. Friends, third point
penny stocks, if you want to do risk free
investment, it is minimalist
investment and if you want to minimize the investment on this, then
stay away from penny stocks because the
payment option is very-very volatile. A little
test. Third point
4.0 finally Bigg Boss, start invalidating such companies. You use it
in daily use,
for example, what is your routine in daily use, you
wake up in the morning, you brush your teeth, you go to
make up your hair, you use shampoo or soap,
again there are many companies for this too.
Third, my favorite is Saif, car insurance is
coming.  I had to make the payment for health insurance and motor insurance through the
bank's website. I do
n't have any money in the bank, so now I have to make the
payment through a credit card.
I have to travel by train and book the ticket online.
So friends, I just
told you a common sense of how you
can divide this company, you
use it in your daily routine. So this was
in section 1, section 12. Friends, now we
will see how to weight the finance
company and which one is 5.3 over, it is of finance.
So friends, in this section we will see what
should be the final cut off of the company so that
we can default the size of the company,
which I call 5.3 over.
To show this 5.5 work, I will take the help of a
website called screenr.com. This is a
very super website where you
can do a lot of final cut off and data panelists.
I will tell you how to do this. So go to
screenr.in,
click on screens here. So
friends, this screen option gives
you the option to select different parameters.  It provides a
provision where you
can create different screens.
Now after clicking on it, I
will share that point with you and will present it to you on this very website.
Point number one,
any company should have continuous sales growth
and it should be above one percent.
So the first parameter is that growth
of three years should be B grade tonic eight
percent. So friends, this percentage is just a number.
This is my computer that I am comfortable with the
company which is growing sales more than eight percent.
This is the cut off,
hence I can give a slightly lower number here,
but unemployed companies can update your numbers.
You can update this. The second most
important thing is profit. So now let us
see that the profit growth of any company
this year should be greater than eight
percent. So, point number two, this
point number 3,
how much return is being generated on the money invested in equity. This is
nothing but return on equity. So, the third
parameter is friends, how much is the average return on
equity coming out?  If ₹100 is giving a fifteen
percent return on equity, then
I am happy with this cut-off.
Friends, this is a low number. If it is above this, then it
is better. Okay, Sudeshwar. Third
parameter for parameter is that the promoters should
not have any shares or share percentage plate. By plate, I mean
job security. They should not have kept their duty for some time. So
please, the percentage should
also be soft
0.2. Number five is the margins of the company.
I mean,
what percent operating profit is coming from sales of ₹100. So, the
operating profit margin should be
more than ten percent. So this
point and basic health tips. Apart from this,
I also look at the debt of the company.
Friends, this is very important. A lead is complete.
But I will
not enter the debt to equity ratio here because it will
eliminate the banks. So, that is why I will
enter the CO point here and run the query.
After doing the same, friends, all those
companies will open in front of you which have
these parameters.  And those in which
Shetty margin is good, then
friends, more or less pieces. After this, the
next step I do immediately is to
put it in descending order of market cap. So the more market capitalization of the
company, the better. I would
prefer companies with the same market cap
index numbers. So, here I
put the market cap, so these are my
companies in descending order. Friends, friends, take a look at
this list pack here: HDFC
Bank, Bajaj Finance, SSC CGL, Nestle,
Bajaj Auto, SBI Cards. Now think about
which of these companies' products do you use in your daily routine.
You should shortlist the company which you are convinced of in the section for further
evaluation. So,
friends, these are Vidmate companies from the 5-point
framework. So,
friends, the images pack of the 5-point framework,
all these low-fee chocolates
came in front of us. So, obviously,
I cannot weight all of these.
For further analysis, we have to sample the products
whose products I use or
I do transactions.  That is HDFC
Bank. So to evaluate HDFC Bank,
we will look at its other parameters. No doubt,
more details are seen in the bank.
But first let's get a basic idea of ​​how to
further understand this topic. If it is for
educational purposes, then you can see
HDFC Bank. So here first of all, take a
look at the accused. RO is 16.5, a good number.
We had a cutoff of 15. Details about which are good
things moving on here. Now below,
I would like to present before you the competitor analysis.
So here I will
show you the entire comparison. In HDFC Bank, which
in my view is the highest
market cap company, it is in the waiting space
private banking slip. Here, its
five-year PI and current has
not increased much. So here friends, it
shows that if the period or PI
of the bank is done, then HDFC Bank,
Axis Bank, Swift
ICICI Bank has increased from 15 to 20. Kotak
's Ped Samosa Gyan is in that good valuation
terms. Axis Bank  The profit has increased a lot,
but this David C Bank is a guarantee behind this gold and
effective industry. So
comparatively, I like HDFC Bank.
Similarly, if we look at their quarterly results,
their revenue is
increasing consistently quarter by quarter. So in June
2018, there were
2300 units and 810 units, so the
revenue increased for the bank. Similarly,
if I look at their pension profit, it has
increased consistently from
more than 300 units. Last year in June,
they had a final profit of Rs 100 crore,
which has increased gradually in two quarters. But if you pay
attention to the VAT, then this point is in the registry.
But here I would like to share another interesting thing
with you. Their Jio net
profit has gone up to
more than Rs 100 crore. That is a very good
sign, so there is profit growth here too. And
we had also applied this in the 5.3 framework.
PNB has created a quarterly profit, if
we look at the manual year, it is near, then
in the last trailing platform team, it is
showing a net profit of Rs 3000 crore in all the
quarters, so the 10 highest profits
from
2012 or so friends, here
we are seeing profitable companies in the form of
HDFC Bank, now below here the net growth
profit is doing double digit in 3 years, 5 years,
it has reduced a little by one
percent, but more or less
profit growth is also
70% in Impact Wrestling tournament, which is the comedy
and decided, they have shown such good profit,
their return on equity has also been more than 50%
consistently, here, the
middle waiter is good for HDFC Bank, if
we look at the balance sheet, then their profits have increased
from Rs 1400 crore to Rs
209, so one nak 75 crore in
just Twenty20, so this is very very good
sign to see  Friends,
additionally, if they were not adding by channel
and were adding some other cycle, then
I would have also looked at their borrowings.
Capital is hero material for Birds Bank, so
we do not involve the borrowings of the bank, but
here their results are very
positive,
they have generated positive moving average and cashless as well,
last year share holding, I would
like to share this with you,
friends, in share holding, here the public
holding has reduced from 20% to 12%,
this means that the
institutional investors, domestic
one and foreign, have
increased their holding, the holding of two foreign ones has
reduced a little, 5239, but the holding of
domestic and institutional investor's
device has increased by about 50%, this
is a positive sign, so
friends, you are invalid till 25 to 10
minutes, now particular stock Amazon 5.3 is
not exhaustive, let us look at two-three more parameters in the bank
like NPS net
Interest Income Accelerator but you begin with
this framework, you can like all the other staff as well
and you can start
analyzing your stocks.
So friends, this was Prem's plan to do the top-25 in
which Shetty is a little more and
Wrist is a little less. Come, use the framework yourself
and tell me in the comment box below
which company you like from the safety
perspective. Set up having set.
All these staff that I discussed today,
none of them was a director recommendation advice.
This direction should be for educational purposes.
Please consult your financial advisor before
investing in Addison. And you friends, if
you feel that we are doing good work
and you found this video beneficial, then there is a
subscribe button below, definitely press it. Do
n't say anything at all. Happy Nursing friends.